[
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>beon</em>) #### hal — I will be safe",
        "correctAnswer": "beo",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the first person singular form 'beo' as the subject is 'ic'",     
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ðu ana (<em>beon</em>) #### eallra dema — You alone are the judge of all",
        "correctAnswer": "bist",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the second person singular form 'bist' as the subject is 'ðu'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Min sweord (<em>beon</em>) #### min lif — My sword is my life",
        "correctAnswer": "biþ",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the third person singular form 'biþ' as the subject is 'min sweord'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Swa manige (<em>beon</em>) #### men ofer eorþan, swa beoþ modgeþoncas — There are as many viewpoints as there are men on earth",
        "correctAnswer": "beoþ",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is plural form 'beoþ' as the subject is 'men",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic ondræde me for ðam ðe ic (<em>wesan</em>) #### nacod — I am afraid because I am naked",
        "correctAnswer": "eom",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the first person singular form 'eom' as the subject is 'ic'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Sarnys ðe hrepode ond ðu (<em>wesan</em>) #### geunrotsod — Pain touched you and you are made unhappy",
        "correctAnswer": "eart",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the second person singular form 'eart' as the subject is 'ðu'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þearle (<em>wesan</em>) #### me nu min heorte onhæted ond hige geomor swyðe mid sorgum gedrefed — Now my heart is in me sorely inflamed and my mind troubled, deeply afflicted with sorrows",
        "correctAnswer": "is",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the third person singular form 'is' as the subject is 'min heorte'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "(<em>wesan</em>) #### þissa heldora wegas forworhte — These gates of hell are obstructed",
        "correctAnswer": "sind",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the pluralform 'sind' as the subject is 'þissa heldora wegas'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hiericho seo burh (<em>wesan</em>) #### mid weallum ymbtrymed ond fæste belocen — Jericho, the city, was surrounded with walls and firmly locked",
        "correctAnswer": "wæs",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past third person singular form 'wæs' as the subject is 'seo burh'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Forðan ðe ðu (<em>wesan</em>) #### gehyrsum ðines wifes wordum, and min bebod forsawe, þu scealt mid earfoðnyssum þe metes tilian — Because you were obedient to the words of your wife, and despised my commandment, you shall get your food with hardships",
        "correctAnswer": "wære",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past second person singular form 'wære' as the subject is 'ðu'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Drihten (<em>wesan</em>) #### sprecende on sumere tide to his apostolum mid bigspellum — The Lord was speaking at a certain time to his apostles in parables",
        "correctAnswer": "wæs",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past third person singular form 'wæs' as the subject is 'Drihten'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie (<em>wesan</em>) #### gesamnode binnan ðære byrig Hierusalem, six hund ðusend manna — They were assembled within the city of Jerusalem, six hundred thousand men",
        "correctAnswer": "wæron",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past plural form 'wæron' as the subject is 'hie'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ðær ic (<em>beon</em>) #### fægere beþeaht fiðerum ðinum — There I will be pleasantly enveloped in your wings",
        "correctAnswer": "beo",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the first person singular form 'beo' as the subjet is 'ic'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "For ðan ðe ðu ðis dydest, ðu (<em>beon</em>) #### awyrged betweox eallum nytenum and wildeorum — Because you did this, you will be cursed among all the beasts and wild animals",
        "correctAnswer": "bist",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the second person singular form 'beo' as the subject is 'ðu'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hat (<em>beon</em>) #### monegum egeslic æled — The dreadful fire will be hot to many",
        "correctAnswer": "biþ",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the third person singular form 'biþ' as the subject is 'æled'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Swa biþ sæ smilte þonne hie wind ne weceþ, swa (<em>beon</em>) #### þeoda geþwære, þonne hie geþingad habbað — As the sea is calm when the wind doesn't blow, so are people at peace when they have negotiated",
        "correctAnswer": "beoþ",
        "explanation":"Here 'beon' is in the plural form 'beoþ' as the subject is 'þeoda'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>wesan</em>) #### mare þonne þes middangeard, læsse þonne hondwyrm, leohtre þonne mona, swiftre þonne sunne — I am more than this middle world, less than a mite, lighter than the moon, swifter than the sun",
        "correctAnswer": "eom",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the first person singular form 'eom' as the subject is 'ic'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Nu (<em>wesan</em>) #### þu dumb ond deaf — Now you are dumb and deaf",
        "correctAnswer": "eart",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the second person singular form 'eart' as the subject is 'þu'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Her (<em>wesan</em>) #### seo bot hu þu meaht þine æ ceras betan gif hie nellaþ wel weaxan — Here is the remedy how you can restore your fields if they will not grow well",
        "correctAnswer": "is",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the third person singular form 'is' as the subject is 'seo bot'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie cwædon 'Drihten her (<em>wesan</em>) #### twa swurd' — They said, 'Lord, here are two swords'",
        "correctAnswer": "sind",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the plural form 'sind' as the subject is 'twa swurd'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Se Cristendom (<em>wesan</em>) #### swilc on his dæge þæt ælc man hwæt his hade to belumpe folgade se þe wolde — Christianity in his day was such that every man who wanted to would follow what pertained to his order",
        "correctAnswer": "wæs",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past third person singular form 'wæs' as the subject is 'se Cristendom'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Paulus cwæð to Petre: Broðer þu (<em>wesan</em>) #### Gode gecoren ær ic — Paul said to Peter, 'Brother, you were God's chosen before me'",
        "correctAnswer": "wære",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past second person singular form 'wære' as the subject is 'þu'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Freond he (<em>wesan</em>) #### ðurh geleafan ond wiþercora þurh weorc — A friend he was through faith, and a reprobate in works",
        "correctAnswer": "wæs",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past third person singular form 'wæs' as the subject is 'he'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie (<em>wesan</em>) #### swa eaþmode ond swa unscæððige swa þæt cild wæs — They were as humble and as innocent as that child was",
        "correctAnswer": "wæron",
        "explanation":"Here 'wesan' is in the past plural form 'wæron' as the subject is 'hie'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>gan</em>) #### ut on dægræde þywende oxan to felda — I go out at dawn driving oxen to fields",
        "correctAnswer": "ga",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the first person singular form 'ga' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ðu (<em>gan</em>) #### beforan Drihtnes ansyne his wegas gearwian — You go before the face of the Lord to prepare His ways",
        "correctAnswer": "gæst",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the second person singular form 'gæst' as the subject is 'ðu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ver is lengtentima ond he (<em>gan</em>) #### to tune on .vii. idus Februarii — Fair is Spring and he goes to town on 7 to the ides of February",
        "correctAnswer": "gæþ|gæð",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the third person singular form 'gæþ' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He ða gesceop of ðære eorðan eall nytencynn, and deorcynn, ealle ða ðe on feower fotum (<em>gan</em>) #### — He then created of earth all the race of cattle, and the brute race, all those which go on four feet",
        "correctAnswer": "gaþ|gað",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the plural form 'gaþ' as the subject is 'ealle ða ðe on feower fotum'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>gan</em>) #### ða to Godes ðenunge ond ðaet folc gebletsode ond him Godes gerihtu dyde — I went then to God's ministry and blessed the people, and celebrated God's rights before them",
        "correctAnswer": "eode",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past first person singular form 'eode' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þa þu geongre wære, þu gertest þe and (<em>gan</em>) #### þær þu woldest — When you were younger, you used to dress yourself and used to go where you wished",
        "correctAnswer": "eodest",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past second person singular form 'eodest' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He (<em>gan</em>) #### ofer sæ mid drygum fotum ond he gestilde windas mid his hæse — He went over the sea with dry feet, and he stilled the winds by his command",
        "correctAnswer": "eode",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past third person singular form 'eode' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie ða to ðæm symle sittan, (<em>gan</em>) #### wlance to wingedrince, ealle his weagesiðas bealde byrnwiggende — Then they went to sit down to the feast, proud at the wine—drinking, all his woeful companions, bold byrnied warriors",
        "correctAnswer": "eodon",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past plural form 'eodon' as the subject is 'hie'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>gan</em>) #### on minne bate ond rowe ut on þa ea ond weorpe min nett on þa ea — I go into my boat, row out on the water, and cast my net into the water",
        "correctAnswer": "ga",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the first person singular form 'ga' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þu (<em>gan</em>) #### on þinum breoste and etst þa eorðan eallum dagum þines lifes — You go on your breast and eat the earth all the days of your life",
        "correctAnswer": "gæst",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the second person singular form 'gæst' as the subject is 'ðu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þa feng Æscwine to rice, þæs cynes (<em>gan</em>) #### to Cerdice, ond heold .ii. gear —  Then Æscwine succeeded to the kingdom, of that descent which goes back to Cerdic, and held it 2 years",
        "correctAnswer": "gæþ|gæð",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the third person singular form 'gæþ' as the subject is 'þæs cynes'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ne lifað na se man be hlafe anum ac lifað be ðæm wordum ðe (<em>gan</em>) #### of Godes muðe — Man lives not by bread alone, but lives by the words which go from the mouth of God.",
        "correctAnswer": "gaþ|gað",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the plural form 'gaþ' as the subject is 'ðæm wordum'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>gan</em>) #### fram ðæm fæder ond com in ðisne middangeord efersonað — I went from the father and came in this world again",
        "correctAnswer": "eode",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past first person singular form 'eode' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þa cwæð he: 'la freond hu—mæte (<em>gan</em>) #### ðu in' — Then he said, 'Lo! Friend, in what manner went you in?'",
        "correctAnswer": "eodest",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past second person singular form 'eodest' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He (<em>gan</em>) #### cwicu and gesund into his byrgene — He went quick and whole into his grave",
        "correctAnswer": "eode",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past second person singular form 'eode' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þine syll (<em>gan</em>) #### ond ða assan wið hie læswodon; þa færlice comon Sabei ond hie ealle us benamon and ðine yrðlingas ofslogon — Your ploughs went and the asses grazed near; then suddenly Sabaeans came, and they took all of us and killed your plowman",
        "correctAnswer": "eodon",
        "explanation":"Here 'gan' is in the past plural form 'eodon' as the subject is 'Þine syll'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ond ic (<em>don</em>) #### eall swa ge biddaþ — And I will do all as you ask",
        "correctAnswer": "do",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the first person singular form 'do' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hwæt (<em>don</em>) #### þu gif unclæne fiscas beoþ? — What do you do if it is unclean fish?",
        "correctAnswer": "dest",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the second person singular form 'dest' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Gif esne (<em>don</em>) #### his rade þaes daeges, .vi. se wiþ dryhten gebete oþþe sine hyd — If a servant makes a journey of his own on that day, he shall pay 6 shillings compensation to his lord or undergo the lash",
        "correctAnswer": "deþ|deð",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the third person singular form 'deþ' as the subject is 'esne'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ne winne ge ongen ða ðe eow yfel (<em>don</em>) #### — Strive ye not against those who do you wrong",
        "correctAnswer": "doþ|doð",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the plural form 'doþ' as the subject is 'ða ðe'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "On þisse nihte manega þingc ic (<em>don</em>) #### — I did many things on this night",
        "correctAnswer": "dyde",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past first person singular form 'dyde' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þu, cnapa, hwæt (<em>don</em>) #### todæg? — You, boy, what did you do today?",
        "correctAnswer": "dydest",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past second person singular form 'dydest' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ða behydde Adam hine ond his wif eac swa (<em>don</em>) #### — Then Adam hid himself and his wife also did so",
        "correctAnswer": "dyde",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past third person singular form 'dyde' as the subject is 'his wif'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hu ne forealdodon þa gewritu þeah ond losodon, swa some swa þa writeras (<em>don</em>) #### — Would not the writings nevertheless get old and perish, just as the writers did",
        "correctAnswer": "dydon",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the plural form 'dydon' as the subject is 'þa writeras'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic melke hie tweowa on dæge þærto ge cyse ge buteran ic (<em>don</em>) #### ond ic eom getrywe hlaforde minum — I milk them twice a day, then I do the cheese and the butter, and I am faithful to my lord",
        "correctAnswer": "do",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the first person singular form 'do' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hwæt (<em>don</em>) #### þu be þinre huntunge? — What do you do about your catch?",
        "correctAnswer": "dest",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the second person singular form 'dest' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ða se hehsta Dema ædre mid elne onbryrde swa he (<em>don</em>) #### anra gehwylcne herbuendra þe hyne him to helpe seceð — Then the highest judge swiftly inspired her with courage, as He does each person who seeks His help",
        "correctAnswer": "deþ|deð",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the third person singular form 'deþ' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ðæt cild weox swa swa oðre cild (<em>don</em>) #### — The child grew as other children do",
        "correctAnswer": "doþ|doð",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the plural form 'doþ' as the subject is 'oðre cild'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Cumað ond geseoð ðone man ðe me sæde ealle ða ðing ic (<em>don</em>) #### — Come and see the man who said to me all the things I did",
        "correctAnswer": "dyde",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past first person singular form 'dyde' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "God cwæð to ðam wife: Hwi (<em>don</em>) #### ðu ðæt? Heo cwæð: Seo nædre bepæhte me and ic ætt — God said to the woman, 'why did you do that?' She said, 'the snake deceived me and I ate'",
        "correctAnswer": "dydest",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past second person singular form 'dydest' as the subject is 'ðu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "swa he ær on ðæm beame (<em>don</em>) #### — As he did on that tree before",
        "correctAnswer": "dyde",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past third person singular form 'dyde' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Gif we ænige bote gebidan scylan þonne mote we þæs to Gode earnian bet þonne we ær þysan (<em>don</em>) #### — If we shall experience any remedy, then we must deserve that of God better than we have previously done",
        "correctAnswer": "dydon",
        "explanation":"Here 'don' is in the past plural form 'dydon' as the subject is 'we'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic (<em>willan</em>) #### mid flode folc acwellan ond cynna gehwilc cwicra wihta — I intend to kill with a flood the people and every kind of living creature",
        "correctAnswer": "wille",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the first person singular form 'wille' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hwyder (<em>willan</em>) #### ðu ga? — Where do you intend to go?",
        "correctAnswer": "wilt",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the second person singular form 'wilt' as the subject is 'ðu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Se biscop sceal þe (<em>willan</em>) #### onfon Godes mildheortnesse þrafian þa mæssepreostas mid lufe ond mid laþe þæt hie healdan Godes æwe on riht — The bishop that wants to obtain God's mercy, must compel the priests with love and with fear to correctly preserve God’s law",
        "correctAnswer": "wile",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the third person singular form 'wile' as the subject is 'se biscop'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þry dagas to lafe sindon þæt hie þe (<em>willan</em>) #### acwellan — Three days remain before the day comes on which they intend to kill you",
        "correctAnswer": "willaþ|willað",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the plural form 'willaþ' as the subject is 'hie'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Forðy ic (<em>willan</em>) #### ðætte hie ealneg æt ðære stowe wæren — Therefore I wanted them always to be there at that place",
        "correctAnswer": "wolde",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past first person singular form 'wolde' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic geanbidode swiðe wel oð ic wisse hwæt ðu (<em>willan</em>) #### and hu ðu hit understandan woldest — I waited very willingly until I knew what you wanted and how you would understand it",
        "correctAnswer": "woldest",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past second person singular form 'woldest' as the subject is 'ðu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He cwæð ðæt he (<em>willan</em>) #### þæm wife gemyltsian — He said that he wanted to pardon the woman",
        "correctAnswer": "wolde",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past third person singular form 'wolde' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Loð þa eode to his twam aðumum þe (<em>willan</em>) #### wifian on his twam dohtrum — Lot then went to his two sons in law, who intended to marry his two daughters",
        "correctAnswer": "woldon",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past plural form 'woldon' as the subject is 'his twam aðumum'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hwæt (<em>willan</em>) #### ic ðissum wiðersacan geandwyrdan? — What answer will I give to this denial?",
        "correctAnswer": "wille",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the first person singular form 'wille' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Cwædon him to: Gif þu ne (<em>willan</em>) #### us geðafian in swa æðelicum þinge þe we biddað ne meaht þu in usse mægðe ne ussum gemanan wunian — They said to him: 'If you will not consent to us in so noble a matter, as we ask, you may not dwell in our country nor in our society'",
        "correctAnswer": "wilt",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the second person singular form 'wilt' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Elpendes hyd (<em>willan</em>) #### drincan wætan, gelice spynge deð — An elephant’s hide will absorb liquid, like a sponge does",
        "correctAnswer": "wile",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the third person singular form 'wile' as the subject is 'Elpendes hyd'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þonne þy ilcan dæge þe hie hine to þæm ade beran (<em>willan</em>) #### todælað hie his feoh — Then on the same day when they intend to bear him to the pyre, they divide his wealth",
        "correctAnswer": "willaþ|willað",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the plural form 'willaþ' as the subject is 'hie'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He nyste hwæt ic (<em>willan</em>) #### — He didn't know what I wanted",
        "correctAnswer": "wolde",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past first person singular form 'wolde' as the subject is 'ic'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hwi (<em>willan</em>) #### þu beswican þæt mære wif Melantian mid forligre? — Why would you entice that excellent woman Melantian with fornication?",
        "correctAnswer": "woldest",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past second person singular form 'woldest' as the subject is 'þu'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Þa Darius geseah þæt he ouerwunnen beon wolde, þa (<em>willan</em>) #### he hiene selfne on ðæm gefeohte forspillan — When Darius saw that he would be overrun, then he wanted to kill himself on the battlefield",
        "correctAnswer": "wolde",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past third person singular form 'wolde' as the subject is 'he'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ond wið þæm þa ðe in oðre wisan don (<em>willan</em>) #### he wæs mid welme micelre ellenwodnisse onbærned — And against those who wanted to do otherwise he was inspired with great fervor and zeal",
        "correctAnswer": "woldon",
        "explanation":"Here 'willan' is in the past plural form 'woldon' as the subject is 'þæm'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    }
]